Hi and welcome to The Winning Factor. I'm Alan Aitken, and on this show each week
we take a look at some upcoming races in Hong Kong, try to identify an angle to
The race that might lead us to finding the winner. Well, it's Saturday racing.
this weekend in Hong Kong, the first race I'm going to take a look at is Race
Ten, where our winning factor is the map. So this is Class 3, 1600 metres.
And Blazing Wukong and Amazing Partners are coming off last start wins.
Endured has been racing well in similar events without much luck.
Smart Avenue should improve with a better draw.
And Family Jewel and Hymnbook both look to have chances as well.
So not a one-horse race by any means.
Quite a few chances.
But I'm looking most closely at a couple of horses I think will cope with what looks quite a tricky event in terms of the map.
And that's Blazing Wukong and Amazing Partners.
Now, Amazing Partners, first of all, well, he's lightly raced.
He's only had six starts for three wins.
And this was his latest when he tackled 1,600 metres for the first time.
This is Race 601. He's in gate four, pink colours.
And Amazing Partners jumps well. He isn't a quick horse naturally.
But Vincent Ho is able to get him into a position near the lead.
through what is a slow first sectional
Before the pace does pick up a little through the middle stages.
but still is only steady.
A number of Saturday's rivals are here too.
In Jude, inside amazing partners in red and grey.
Mr Dapper, the leader, and Himbuk in green near the tail.
Now, the field is bunched here with no serious pace.
and becomes just a dash down the straight
With Endue on the inside having no luck.
But amazing partners, well, he's able to be challenging
at the right time with enough turn of foot
to reel in the leaders and he grinds out the win.
Now, despite his good winning record, three from six amazing partners
I don't really think we've seen the best of him yet
because he's been in several of these kinds of races
where it's just a grinding sort of finish
difficult to get separation on the field.
So he's done well to put that record together
and that could be a key thing in Saturday's race.
Now, Blazing Wukong, on the other hand,
He's a little bit more well explored with 11 starts so far for three wins.
And here's his latest offering.
This is race 643, gate 13 in black colours.
And Blazing Wukong jumps okay, but jockey Andrea Zanido doesn't even think of looking for a more forward position going back to the rear.
Now, that prevents him covering extra ground early.
But we can see on the heat map it's also a disadvantage with the slow early speed here.
The pace is a little better mid-race but never really gets above steady.
Blazing Wukong then sprints well around the field, deceptively fast around the field in
In fact, as they turn into the stretch, he's the one with the acceleration to go and pick.
up the leaders and put them away.
Just like Amazing Partners, not the most impressive win to the eye but what they have in common.
is that each of them had to produce acceleration at the right time, the right place to go and
win the race and as I said I think that's going to be important in the context of Saturday's race.
Now the leaders, Mr. Dapper and With All My Faith, have the outside gates, so that is the hope of the...
side as far as getting a better speed, but it's quite possible they could get across quickly and
then steady the brakes and we might have a similar style of race to what we've been seeing.
There still looks a little speed in it, inside or out, and that's not going to help the likes
of Family Jewel, Endured and others who have wider draws, while Hymnbook and Smart Avenue
have never really shown as much tactical speed yet, regardless of their draw.
Now Blazing Wukong went all the way back last time.
We have seen him ridden like that quite a bit, but he has also had a lot of wider draws.
This time he's got a better draw, so he might even be closer from Barrier Five.
But we do know that Amazing Partners has the tactical speed to be where he needs to be.
be again.
So the tip from me in race 10, Amazing Partners, his winning factor, the map.
It does look a very tricky map, but it could be a stop-start kind of race.
But what we've seen from Amazing Partners, even in those kinds of races, is that he's
able to put himself in the right place. He's
able to accelerate at the right time and that might be the winning recipe for this event.
The other race I want to take a look at on Sunday is the final event, race 11 and our
winning factor here, the draw.
This is Class Two, an excellent Class Two in fact, over 1200 metres and despite the
Talent in the Race, I think we can narrow this down to three really strong chances.
Patch of Stars, who continues to race well.
and two horses we expect to see figuring in some serious races in the future.
Jamie Richards' trained Bulb General and the unbeaten three-year-old Hot Delight.
And I'm most interested in this race in those two lightly raced horses.
As I said, Hot Delight, unbeaten, three from three.
and Bulb General, a year older, and he's three wins from five starts.
Now, firstly, Hot Delight, and his trainer, Francis Loy,
has made comparisons at the same stage with a horse that you might be familiar with that he
used to train Golden Sixty. That's a big call. Certainly there's a lot of water to flow under
the bridge for that one, but he can't be faulted in what he's done so far. This is race 540. He's
in gate seven in yellow and red colours, and Hot Delight jumps well for Vincent Ho and is quickly
Up on the speed, in what you can see is a slow first 400-metre section with Ho on the odds.
on favourite here taking bad luck out of the equation.
Now the pace does lift a little as the race progresses then becomes a strong sprint home.
down the stretch.
The leader fights on well but ultimately Hot Delight is too good and comes clear to win.
with some conviction.
Now, perhaps to the eye, not deserving the kind of boom that we're talking about on this horse.
But the way the race was run there meant that to win it the way he did,
Hot Delight had to break 44 seconds for his last 800 metres.
And that's the kind of sustained speed that is going to make this young horse.
A star of the future as he develops and grows stronger.
As to Bold General, well, as I mentioned, he's a year older.
And really, he was this time last year where Hot Delight is now.
He was an up-and-comer with a great turn of foot as a three-year-old.
He took that into his early starts as a four-year-old.
but then his career was interrupted by injury.
He's only had the one run back in March.
and let's have a look at how he handled that.
This is Race 562, gate seven here in orange and white colours.
Bulb General jumps well for Zac Purton.
but this race is a contrast with the one that we just saw
as the early speed here is pretty good.
Zak let Bulb General find his feet as is usual, and he ends up towards the rear with
another of Saturday's rivals Patch of Stars in yellow, white and blue a few lengths ahead
of him on the rail.
Now the pace increases again mid-race so it's really run to suit horses off the pace.
When they straighten up, Patch of Stars comes to pounce; he comes up short behind Young.
Champion with Bob General working home steadily into third.
Now Bob General will meet the first two that beat him home there on Saturday, but they
were hard race-fit horses and he was coming off quite a lengthy break.
So I do think he's going to tighten up and be a better version of himself on Saturday.
But I think when we go to the draw, that's where things are really getting interesting.
in this race.
There's good speed out wide here from Victor the winner, Crimson Flash and Lady's Choice.
So the tempo looks sound enough.
Bob General is drawn lower this time, while he's still not going to be on the front end.
of the race.
His jockey this time, Joe Moreira, should be able to use that draw to get a nice trip.
through the race.
Harry Bentley takes over on Hot Delight with the light weight, but his map looks filled.
with a lot of decisions to make, and tough ones they are.
We saw Hot Delight up on the speed, his last two starts in slow tempos, but with a better
pace and a wide draw here he would have trouble getting to a similar spot without covering ground
and working and might even have to drag all the way back in the field so that he doesn't have a
difficult run, so the tip from me in race 11 is Bulb General. His winning factor, the draw now had they
Drawn the other way around, I'm sure that I would have been tipping Hot Delight, but his job looks
full of difficulties. He's good enough to overcome them. I certainly don't want to
say it's lights out for his chances but it brings him back to the older horse
who has drawn better this time, Bold General, and should be fitter than he was
for that first up run. Well, that's it from The Winning Factor this week. Good
luck on Saturday. We'll see you next time.