Chinese subtitles provided
Cornflakes
Cats, I love cats so much.
I love watching it, even during Chinese New Year.
So South Africa also celebrates its own New Year.
It's only just New Year.
New 10-pound apprentice jockey Yuen Hang-yiu attended today's press conference.
Generously sharing their own hobbies.
Confident and sunny responses.
With a sincere smile, she really gained points.
Her current biggest goal is...
Just trying to absorb as much experience as possible.
Strive for continuous self-improvement.
My strength is my own prediction of the due date.
Hoping to perform even better.
If Han, I am still looking for you.
We hope there will be no further incidents like this.
Of course, I will fully dedicate myself to continuous improvement.
I always pay close attention to every jockey.
Because every jockey has their own unique qualities.
And there are benefits to them as well.
Moreover, their jockey pairings differ.
So I hope to draw on each jockey's strengths.
It is best if it fits oneself.
March 8
Jockey Ashley Low officially becomes a father.
Son Thomas was born in Hong Kong.
Also has a foot at the end.
on the day of birth
Jockey Siu Lai Ngai won four races in a single day.
Many friends and horse racing fans
Many people flocked to her social media platforms.
Sending full blessings to this new couple of parents.
Hope Thomas continues to shine as a little lucky charm.
Leading his father to chase more victories.
Baby formula money depends on you continuing to watch.
Apart from Ai Siu-li, who is celebrating two joys at once,
Another jockey
Recently, a god-tier performance that left everyone stunned unfolded.
It is Macdonald.
March 7
The race day was held at Sha Tin Racecourse.
Won six races in a single day.
including Group One races.
Kentucky Derby
The most affordable legendary jockey, Moreira.
That is the record set by Pat's father-in-law in 1987.
It is also the first time in 38 years that someone has...
Sydney's City Racecourse replicates a historic six-win day.
It absolutely shook the entire Australian racing world.
Recently, citizens were near Sha Tin Racecourse.
Recognized a cute little horse.
Peering out of a stable window to enjoy the view.
Everyone says she is very cute.
However, some sharp-eyed netizens noticed.
The pony seems to have dropped something; what could it be?
It turns out it was this pile of grass.
Everyone is worried that if the horse misses a meal, it will go hungry.
This sparked a frenzy of reposts among netizens.
Fortunately, the shop succeeded in summoning stable staff.
Besides providing lunch for the horses,
Also revealing the mysterious horse's true identity to everyone.
It turns out these willful yet adorable protagonists
It comes from Lucky Style in Yau Tat Wing's stable.
Everyone, next time you pass by the racecourse area
They can also wave hello from a distance.
On March 9, Australian jockey Steven Ray.
Jockey Maw Long-wong was removed from his mount.
Highland Blink, a popular and fast-paced horse.
Won the Adelaide Cup.
Two horses, heads only, for a photo.
Only then was the winner decided.
So thrilling.
but they crossed the finish line first.
Secured biggest victory by dismounting the jockey.
Stenley was unseated by Mawlong Wang.
The highlight of life's journey.
Instantly turned into a disaster scene.
Many netizens have reacted to the incident.
It has become the latest meme through CAPTO.
Everyone is truly happy for him.
Like taking a flight a few days ago.
Besides Stephen, he also received a cabin upgrade.
The crew also prepared for him.
Special welcome ceremony.
It was all passengers on board.
Let's celebrate the night race together.
Such a large bottle cup.
The most suitable occasion for drinking champagne.
Next Sunday is the BMW Hong Kong.
The big day of the Grand Cup race.
And the draw ceremony for the race positions
It will take place on March 19.
Everyone remember to pay attention.
Which contestant will draw the lucky prize?
We will follow up with everyone next week.
Latest updates on the major tournament.