Next month, new jockeys arrive: Australian star Bobby Prebble and apprentice Yuen Hang-yiu. Both attended trials on Tuesday; Yuen rode three horses for trainer Yiu Bun-fai and held a press conference with the media.
Cornflakes
Cat Super likes cats.
I love watching it; I watch it every New Year.
So South Africans also watch Nicolas Cage for New Year.
Happy New Year and prosperity.
New 10-pound apprentice jockey Yuen Hang-yiu attended today's press conference.
Openly sharing their personal interests.
Confident and sunny responses.
With a sincere smile, she truly wins over fans.
Her current biggest goal is...
Just trying to absorb as much experience as possible.
Strive for continuous self-improvement.
My strength is my own jockeying skills.
Hopes to perform even better.
I am still looking for my weaknesses.
Hope there will be no further incidents.
Of course, I will continuously improve in all aspects.
Of course, I always pay close attention to every jockey.
Because every jockey has their own unique qualities.
And their benefits as well.
Moreover, their riding styles also differ.
So I hope to benefit from every jockey's support.
Keeping it for oneself is best.
March 8th.
Jockey Eddie Ahl has officially become a father.
Thomas was born in Hong Kong.
It's even better with a footrest.
on the day of birth
Adkins won four races in a single day.
Many friends and horse racing fans
flooded into her social media platforms.
Sending full blessings to this new couple.
Hope Thomas continues to shine as a little lucky charm.
Leading his father to chase more victories.
Baby formula money depends on you keeping it going strong.
Besides Ai Siu-lei, who is celebrating two joys at once.
Another jockey
Recently, a god-tier performance unfolded that left people stunned with victory.
It's Macdonald.
March 7th
The race day was held at Sha Tin Racecourse.
Winning six races in a single day.
Including Group One races.
Kentucky Derby
Tied legendary jockey Zac Purton's record.
That was a record set by Paul's father-in-law in 1987.
It is also the first time in 38 years that someone has...
Sydney's City Racecourse witnessed a feat of six wins in one day.
Absolutely shook the entire Australian horse racing world.
Recently, citizens were near Sha Tin Racecourse.
Recognized a cute little horse.
The horse poked its head out of the window to enjoy the view.
Everyone says she is very cute.
However, discerning netizens noticed.
The horse seems to have dropped something; what could it be?
So it was these grasses.
Everyone is worried the horse might miss lunch and go hungry.
This triggered widespread reposting by netizens.
Fortunately, this shop successfully summoned stable staff to intervene.
Besides supplementing the horses' lunch,
Also revealing the true identity of the mysterious horse.
It turns out this willful yet cute protagonist
Lucky Style from Yau Tai-wing's stable.
Everyone, next time you pass by the racecourse area
They can also greet him from a distance.
On March 9, Australian jockey Steve Donoghue.
Riding on Mei Long Wang's back.
Defeated favorite Highland.
Bling won the Adelaide Cup.
Two horses, heads only, for a photo.
to determine the winner first.
So thrilling.
But it was regrettable crossing the finish line.
Achieved the biggest victory of his riding career.
Stenley was thrown out by the American Wolf King.
Peak moments in life.
Instantly turned into a disaster scene.
Many netizens have reacted to the incident.
Updated from Capt's image to the latest face.
Everyone is truly happy for him.
Like taking a flight a few days ago.
Stenley
Besides receiving a cabin upgrade, crew members also prepared for her.
Crew also prepared a special welcome ceremony for him.
It was all passengers on board.
Gathered together to celebrate the night race for him.
Such a large trophy.
Most suitable for drinking champagne.
Next Sunday is the BMW Hong Kong.
The big day of the Derby race.
And the draw ceremony for the starting positions.
It will take place on March 19.
Everyone, please remember to pay attention.
Which racing horse will draw a favorable gate?
We will follow up with everyone next week.
Latest updates on the major tournament.